<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to ISNET on ISNET Series Website</title>
    <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to ISNET on ISNET Series Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 09:44:34 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isnet-series.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basics</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/mcmc/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/mcmc/basics/</guid>
      <description>This section is concerned with all things Markov Chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) relevant to ISNET topics. Learn what is MCMC, how to use it, and popular computing packages to perform sampling on your problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computing resources</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/mcmc/computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/mcmc/computing/</guid>
      <description>This page links to relevant computing resources for MCMC and has some discussion of how they are useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced topics</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/mcmc/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/mcmc/advanced/</guid>
      <description>This page is for cutting edge MCMC topics beyond getting started and what package to use for sampling. s</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/education/schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/resources/education/schools/</guid>
      <description>This page links to schools and training courses and their resources.
 Learning from Data: Bayesian Methods and Machine Learning. This links to a course webpage and github repository for a Nuclear TALENT (Training in Low Energy Nuclear Theory) course held at the University of York in York, UK from June 10 to 28, 2019  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISNET meetings</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/isnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/isnet/</guid>
      <description>The ISNET series of international meetings started in 2012 with a one-day workshop in Krakow, Poland and has been held since in both Europe and the United States. See this editorial in the Journal of Physics G and this article in Nuclear Physics News on the first ISNET workshop in Krakow.
Upcoming meetings  2021: This meeting is planned to be held in late 2021 at Michigan State University in East Lansing, USA after it was not possible to hold the in-person workshop in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Related meetings</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/related-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/related-meetings/</guid>
      <description>This pages lists meetings related to the ISNET series, with links to talks and other resources if available.
 Meetings in 2020 Uncertainties in Calculations of Nuclear Reactions of Astrophysical Interest A virtual workshop was hosted by the Mainz Institute for Theoretical Physics.
Available talks can be found on the timetable page.
Artificial Intelligence for Nuclear Physics 2020 A three-day workshop entitled &amp;ldquo;A.I. for Nuclear Physics&amp;rdquo; was held in 2020 at Jefferson Lab in Newport News, VA, USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JPhysG Special Issues</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/publications/jphysg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 09:55:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/publications/jphysg/</guid>
      <description>The Journal of Physics G: Nuclear and Particle Physics from IOP publishing has an ongoing history of special issues focused on ISNET.
 2015: Enhancing the interaction between nuclear experiment and theory through information and statistics (ISNET) 2019: Focus on further enhancing the interaction between nuclear experiment and theory through information and statistics (ISNET 2.0)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
