<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings on ISNET Series Website</title>
    <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings on ISNET Series Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 09:55:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>APS DNP 2019</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/dnp-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 13:58:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/dnp-2019/</guid>
      <description>A half-day workshop entitled &amp;ldquo;New data analysis methods&amp;rdquo; was held at the 2019 American Physical Society Division of Nuclear Physics meeting in Arlington, VA, USA. The talks from that meeting are hosted here for further dissemination.
 Talk 1: Introduction to Bayesian methods and uncertainty quantification by Sarah Wesolowski (Salisbury U) Talk 2: Application of Bayesian methods in effective field theory by Dick Furnstahl (Ohio State U) Talk 3: Uncertainty quantification in Nuclear Reactions by Filomena Nunes (FRIB/ Michigan State U) Talk 4: Bayesian analysis and interpretation of heavy-ion collisions by Scott Pratt (Michigan State U) Talk 5: Fitting with normalization uncertainties by Byron Roe (U of Michigan) Talk 6: Global fits for deep inelastic scattering and related processes by Nobuo Sato (Jefferson Lab)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISNET meetings</title>
      <link>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/isnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 12:32:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isnet-series.github.io/meetings/isnet/</guid>
      <description>The ISNET series of international meetings started in 2012 with a one-day workshop in Krakow, Poland and has been held since in both Europe and the United States. See this editorial in the Journal of Physics G and this article in Nuclear Physics News on the first ISNET workshop in Krakow.
 2012: First one-day workshop held in Krakow, Poland. 2013: ISNET: Information and Statistics in Nuclear Experiment and Theory, held in Glasgow, Scotland, UK.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>